<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Book>
    <book_title>Guide to <location visitable="yes">Balmora</location></book_title>

    <writer listed="no"> Anonymous </writer>

    <Acquisition> 
        <NPC who="Codus Callonus">Codus Callonus</NPC>
        <NPC who="Dorisa Darvel">Dorisa Darvel</NPC> 
        <NPC who="Falvel Arenim"> Falvel Arenim </NPC> 
        <NPC who="Phane Rielle"> Phane Rielle </NPC> 
        <NPC who="Segunivus Mantedius"> Segunivus Mantedius </NPC> 
        <NPC who="Sovor Trandel"> Sovor Trandel </NPC> 
        "random_book_imperial_dunmer" <item>(randomized item)</item>
    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        <location visitable="yes"><location visitable="yes">Balmora</location></location> is the
        district seat of House Hlaalu, and the largest settlement on <location visitable="yes"
            >Vvardenfell</location> after <location visitable="yes">Vivec City</location>. <location
            visitable="yes">Balmora</location>'s four districts are <location visitable="yes">High
            Town</location>, the <location visitabe="yes">Commercial District</location>, <location
            visitable="yes">Labor Town</location>, and <location visitable="yes">Fort
            Moonmoth</location>. <location visitable="yes">High Town</location>, on the hill to the
        west, has the <location visitable="yes">Tribunal Temple</location>, <location
            visitable="yes">Hlaalu Council Hall</location>, rich manors, better shops, and the
            <location visitable="yes">Morag Tong guildhall</location>. <location visitable="yes">The
                <location visitabe="yes">Commercial District</location></location>, just west of the
        river, is centered on the large plaza north of South Gate, with the <location
            visitable="yes">strider port along the south wall</location>, east of South Gate. The
        Fighters Guild and Mages Guild, and most of <location visitable="yes">Balmora</location>'s
        shops and inns, are located along the streets of the <location visitabe="yes">Commercial
            District</location>. <location visitable="yes">Labor Town</location>, east of the river,
        where the commoners and poor live, has several modest cornerclubs and a few merchants.
            <location visitable="yes">Fort Moonmoth</location>, a long walk southeast of town,
        houses the Legion garrison and the Imperial cult. Services House Hlaalu services are
        available at <location visitable="yes">Hlaalu Council Manor</location> in <location
            visitable="yes">High Town</location>. Temple faithful seek solace and services at the
            <location visitable="yes">Balmora Temple</location> in the southeast. Outlanders must
        travel outside the town walls, through South Gate and east along well-marked roads to
            <location visitable="yes">Fort Moonmoth</location> for Imperial Legion and the Imperial
        cult services. The guildhalls of the Fighters Guild and Mages Guild are on the street north
        from the plaza in the <location visitabe="yes">Commercial District</location>. Morag Tong
        services are available at their guildhall in the extreme northwest of <location
            visitable="yes"><location visitable="yes">High Town</location></location>. Better shops
        are in <location visitable="yes">High Town</location> on the hill, with numerous merchants
        in the <location visitable="yes">Commercial District</location>, west of the river, and a
        few traders in <location visitable="yes">Labor Town</location>, east of the river. Notable
        Figures None of the Hlaalu counselors live in <location visitable="yes">Balmora</location>.
            <NPC who="Nileno Dorvayn>Nileno Dorvayn"/> at the Council Hall is the ranking Hlaalu
        local. At the Fighters Guild, Eydis Fire-Eye is the steward. <NPC who="Ranis Athrys">Ranis
            Athrys</NPC> is the Mages Guild steward. <NPC who="Ethasi Rilvayn">Ethasi Rilvayn</NPC>
        is the Morag Tong steward. <NPC who="Feldrelo Sadri">Feldrelo Sadri</NPC> is the ranking
        cleric of the <location visitable="yes">Balmora Tribunal Temple</location>. The colorful
            <NPC who="'Sugar Lips' Habasi">'Sugar Lips' Habasi</NPC>, a freelance facilitator of no
        fixed address, is often rumored to be the local boss of the Thieves Guild. Transportation A
        good road leads south to <location visitable="yes">Pelagiad</location>, <location
            visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location>, <location visitable="yes">Ebonheart</location>,
        and <location visitable="yes">Vivec</location>. A rugged wilderness track leads southwest
        along the Odai River to the fishing village of <location visitable="yes">Hla Oad</location>.
        Improved roads head north to Caldera and <location visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>. The
        silt strider port is on the west side of the river near South Gate. Silt strider service
        goes to <location visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location visitable="yes"
            >Suran</location>, <location visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, and <location
            visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location>. Guild guides at the Mages Guild can teleport you
        to <location visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location visitable="yes"
        >Vivec</location>, <location visitable="yes">Caldera</location>, and <location
            visitable="yes">Sadrith Mora</location> for a fee. <location visitable="yes">Hla
            Oad</location> is southwest on the coast. An unimproved trail leads northeast up the
        ravines of <location visitable="yes">Foyada Mamaea</location> to <location visitable="yes"
            >Ghostgate</location>; the path is easy to follow, but dangerous beasts threaten
        pilgrims who travel this route to <location visitable="yes">Ghostgate</location>
        shrine.</contents>

</Book>
