<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="36 Lessons of Vivec Sermon 1">36 Lessons of Vivec Sermon 1</book_title>
    <writer who="Vivec" listed="yes">Vivec</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Falas Ancestral Tomb" visitable="yes">Falas Ancestral Tomb</location>
        <location ref="Molag Mar" visitable="yes">Molag Mar</location>
        <person ref="Vasesius Viciulus">Vasesius Viciulus: Trader</person>
    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        <p>He was born in the ash among the <group ref="Velothi">Velothi</group>, anon <group ref="Chimer">Chimer</group>, before the war with the northern
            men. <person ref="Almalexia">Ayem</person> came first to the village of the netchimen, and her shadow was that of
            Boethiah, who was the Prince of Plots, and things unknown and known would fold
            themselves around her until they were like stars or the messages of stars. <person ref="Almalexia">Ayem</person> took a
            netchiman's wife and said:</p>

        <p><narration who="Almalexia">'I am the Face-Snaked Queen of the Three in One. In you is an image and a seven-syllable
            spell, AYEM AE SEHTI AE VEHK, which you will repeat to it until mystery comes.'</narration></p>

        <p>Then <person ref="Almalexia">Ayem</person> threw the netchiman's wife into the ocean water where <group ref="Dreughs">dreughs</group> took her into
            castles of glass and coral. They gifted the netchiman's wife with gills and milk
            fingers, changing her sex so that she might give birth to the image as an egg. There she
            stayed for seven or eight months.</p>

        <p>Then <person ref="Seht">Seht</person> came to the netchiman's wife and said:</p>

        <p>'I am the Clockwork King of the Three in One. In you is an egg of my brother-sister, who
            possesses invisible knowledge of words and swords, which you shall nurture until the
            <person ref="Hortator">Hortator</person> comes.'</p>

        <p>And <person ref="Seht">Seht</person> then extended his hands and multitudes of homunculi came forth, each like a
            glimmering rope through the water, and they raised the netchiman's wife back to the
            surface world and set her down on the shoals of <location ref= "Azura's Coast" visitable="yes">Azura's Coast</location>. There she lay for seven
            or eight more months, caring for the egg-knowledge by whispering to it the Codes of
            <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person> and the prophecies of Veloth and even the forbidden teachings of <person ref="Trinimac">Trinimac</person>.</p>

        <p>Seven <group ref="Daedra">Daedra</group> came to her one night and each one gave to the egg new motions that could be
            achieved by certain movements of the bones. These are called the Barons of Move Like
            This. Then an eighth Daedroth came, and he was a <group ref="Demiprince">Demiprince</group>, called <person ref="Fa-Nuit-Hen">Fa-Nuit-Hen</person>, or the
            Multiplier of Motions Known. And <person ref="Fa-Nuit-Hen">Fa-Nuit-Hen</person> said:</p>

        <p>'Whom do you wait for?'</p>

        <p>To which the netchiman's wife said to the <person ref="Hortator">Hortator</person>.</p>

        <p>'Go to the land of the <group ref="Indoril">Indoril</group> in three months' time, for that is when war comes. I
            return now to haunt the warriors who fell and still wonder why. But first I show you
            this.'</p>

        <p>Then the Barons and the <group ref="Demiprince">Demiprince</group> joined together into a pillar of fighting styles
            terrible to behold and they danced before the egg and its learning image.</p>

        <p>'Look, little Vehk, and find the face behind the splendor of my bladed carriage, for in
            it is delivered the unmixed conflict path, perfect in every way. What is its
            number?'</p>

        <p>It is said the number is the number of birds that can nest in an ancient tibrol tree,
            less three grams of honest work, but <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> in his later years found a better one and so
            gave this secret to his people.</p>

        <p>'For I have crushed a world with my left hand,' he will say, 'but in my right hand is how
            it could have won against me. Love is under my will only.'</p>

        <p>The ending of the words is ALMSIVI.</p>
    </contents>
</Book>
