<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Grasping Fortune">Grasping Fortune</book_title>
    <writer listed="yes" who="Dram Bero">Dram Bero</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Ald'ruhn, Llether Vari: Enchanter" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn, Llether Vari:
            Enchanter</location>
        <location ref="Caldera, Valvius Mevureius' House" visitable="yes">Caldera, Valvius
            Mevureius' House</location>
        <location ref="Dagon Fel, Heifnir: Trader" visitable="yes">Dagon Fel, Heifnir:
            Trader</location>
        <location ref="Indarys Manor, Manor Services" visitable="yes">Indarys Manor, Manor
            Services</location>

        <location ref="Mournhold, Mournhold Temple: Office of the Lord Archcanon TR" visitable="yes"
            >Mournhold, Mournhold Temple: Office of the Lord Archcanon TR</location>
        <location ref="Ravel Ancestral Tomb" visitable="yes">Ravel Ancestral Tomb</location>
        <location ref="Rethan Manor, Gols' House" visitable="yes">Rethan Manor, Gols'
            House</location>
        <location ref="Suran, Oran Manor" visitable="yes">Suran, Oran Manor</location>
        <location ref="Tel Vos, Tel Vos Central Tower" visitable="yes">Tel Vos, Tel Vos Central
            Tower</location>
        <location ref="Tower of Tel Fyr, Hall of Fyr" visitable="yes">Tower of Tel Fyr, Hall of
            Fyr</location>
        <location ref="Vivec City" visitable="yes">Vivec City</location>
    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        <p>I am a councilor of House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> and chose to write this short guide for those who seek
            to understand us or join us. House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> is the most open and modern of the Great
            Houses. We are the only Great House who has embraced the irresistible tides of Imperial
            law and custom. And thus we have profited by the <group ref = "Empire">Empire</group>'s new policies, rising from
            obscurity as the Greatest of the Houses.</p>

        <p>In the great wind of progress, tradition cannot stand.</p>

        <p>The <group ref = "Redoran">Redoran</group> may surpass us on the field of battle, but when the dust clears, they will
            find themselves indebted to us. The House <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> may know many arcane secrets, but
            they fight among themselves more than against each other, and they cannot adapt to the
            ways of the <group ref = "Empire">Empire</group>. Ancient and powerful though a <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> wizard may be, no individual
            can withstand the march of history. The <group ref = "Indoril">Indoril</group> are loved by the people for their gifts
            and donations, but when the money runs dry, will the people remember? The <group ref = "Dres">Dres</group> know how
            to make money, but they have not learned how not to make enemies.</p>

        <p>Grasp fortune by the forelocks. When you see your chances, seize them.</p>

        <p>When you see a chance to turn a profit, take it. But do not follow money blindly. There
            is value in reputation, more than many young <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> realize. This value must be
            carefully balanced against the more tangible coins in any deal. Theft and murder are bad
            for business. You can steal from someone, but will he trade with you after that? You
            can't bargain with a dead man.</p>

        <p>There are many ways to do business.</p>

        <p>In House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> you must be fast and agile. You must be able to keep up with business and
            with the times. You must be able to speak quickly and convincingly. You must be able to
            trade with the best of merchants and make a profit. You must learn to protect your own
            property by securing it with hidden chests, locks, and even traps. And when
            confrontation is unavoidable, it is best to fight quickly in comfortable, light armors
            with short blades, or to fight from a distance with a marksman's weapons.</p>

        <p>Then, reader, would you seize this opportunity to join House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group>? Would you have
            yourself be counted among the victors in the race for success? Then submit yourself for
            examination at the Balmora Council Manor. If you have the skills, you will be welcome.
            And if you have the will, you may serve House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group>, and advance in the ranks, for
            above all things, House <group ref = "Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> prizes initiative and ambition. </p>
    </contents>
</Book>
