<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref ="Guide to Vvardenfell">Guide to Vvardenfell</book_title>
    <writer listed = "no">Anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <person ref = "Dorisa Darvel">Dorisa Darvel</person>
        <location ref = "Gnaar Mok, Druegh-jigger's Rest" visitable = "yes">Gnaar Mok, Druegh-jigger's Rest</location>
        <location ref = "Tel Uvirith, Tel Uvirith Tower Upper" visitable = "yes">Tel Uvirith, Tel Uvirith Tower Upper</location>
    </Acquisition>
    
    <contents>
<p>        <location ref = "Morrowind" visitable = "yes">Morrowind</location> is the northeastmost province of the Tamrielic Empire, bounded on the north and east by the <location ref = "Sea of Ghosts" visitable = "yes">Sea of Ghosts</location>, on the west by <location ref = "Skyrim" visitable = "no">Skyrim</location>, on the southwest by <location ref = "Cyrodiil" visitable = "yes">Cyrodiil</location> (also known as the Imperial Province), and on the south by <location ref = "Black Marsh" visitable = "yes">Black Marsh</location> (also known as Argonia). <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> District encompasses Vvardefell [sic] Island, a great land mass dominated by the giant volcano <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location> and cut off from mainland <location ref = "Morrowind" visitable = "yes">Morrowind</location> by the surrounding <location ref = "Inner Sea" visitable = "yes">Inner Sea</location>.</p>
        
<p>        Only recently open to settlement and trade, most of the island's population is confined to the relatively hospitable west and southwest coast, centered on the ancient city of <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> and the old Great House district centers at <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>, <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, and <location ref = "Sadrith Mora" visitable = "yes">Sadrith Mora</location>. The rest of the island is covered by hostile desert wastes, arid grasslands, and volcanic badlands, and thinly populated by the nomadic <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group> tribes.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> has nine basic geographic regions, each with their own distinctive plants and terrain features. Scholars have based their classifications on the different types of land described by the native <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s, so the designations are recognized by most local traders, travelers, and adventurers. These geographic regions are called: the <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location>, the <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location>, <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location>, the <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location>, the Grazelands, <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location>, <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location>, the West Gash, and <location ref = "Sheogorad" visitable = "yes">Sheogorad</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location></p>
<p>        The <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location> is a region of lush, green, well-watered southern lowlands where most of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>'s agriculture is found. The area includes <location ref = "Pelagiad" visitable = "yes">Pelagiad</location>, <location ref = "Suran" visitable = "yes">Suran</location>, <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City, and <location ref = "Ald Sotha" visitable = "yes">Ald Sotha</location> along with the inland lakes and waterways of the <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location> proper. The urban areas of <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> and <location ref = "Ebonheart" visitable = "yes">Ebonheart</location> of the southern coast are densely populated; the inland <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location> are dotted with small farms and large plantations. The climate is temperate and comfortable, with moderate rainfall.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Ebonheart" visitable = "yes">Ebonheart</location> is the seat of the Imperial government for <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> district, and a busy center of maritime trade. <location ref = " Castle Ebonheart" visitable = "yes">Castle Ebonheart</location> is the home of <person ref = "Duke Vedam Dren">Duke Vedam Dren</person>, the district's ruler and Emperor's representative. Also located at <location ref = "Castle Ebonheart" visitable = "yes">Castle Ebonheart</location> are the <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> District Council chambers and the <group ref = "Hawk Moth Legion garrison">Hawk Moth Legion garrison</group>. The officers, docks, and warehouses of the <group ref = "East Empire Company">East Empire Company</group> are also found in <location ref = "Ebonheart" visitable = "yes">Ebonheart</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City is the largest settlement on <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>, and one of the largest cities in the East. Each of the great cantons is the size of a complete town. The <person ref = "High Fane">High Fane</person> and the palace of <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> are visited by hundreds of tourists and <group ref = "pilgrims">pilgrims</group> daily. Citizens flock to the <location ref = "Arena" visitable = "yes">Arena</location> for entertainments and war games. Outlanders mostly confine themselves to the <location ref = "Foreign Canton" visitable = "yes">Foreign Canton</location>, while natives live, work, and shop in the Great House compounds and residential cantons.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Ald Sotha" visitable = "yes">Ald Sotha</location> is a splendid Daedric ruin within sight of <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City. Though exotic and picturesque, it is a dangerous site, haunted by old magics, dark cultists, and their Daedric summonings, and not recommended for sightseers.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Suran" visitable = "yes">Suran</location> is an agricultural village in the northeastern corner of the fertile <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location> region. Two popular pilgrimage sites are nearby -- the <location ref = "Fields of Kummu" visitable = "yes">Fields of Kummu</location> and the <location ref = "Molag Bal's Shrine" visitable = "yes">Molag Bal's Shrine</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Pelagiad" visitable = "yes">Pelagiad</location> is a newly chartered Imperial village between <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location> and <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City on the western edge of the <location ref = "Ascadian Isles" visitable = "yes">Ascadian Isles</location> region. The village is right outside the Imperial Legion garrison at Fort <location ref = "Pelagiad" visitable = "yes">Pelagiad</location>. The houses and shops are built in the Western Imperial style, and <location ref = "Pelagiad" visitable = "yes">Pelagiad</location> looks more like a village in the western Empire than a <location ref = "Morrowind" visitable = "yes">Morrowind</location> settlement.</p>
        
<p>        The <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location></p>
<p>        The <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location> are the dry, inhospitable wastelands surrounding the lower slopes of <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location>. The <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location> extend to the <location ref = "Sea of Ghosts" visitable = "yes">Sea of Ghosts</location> in the north, and elsewhere form a wide margin between the blighted <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location> region and other geographic regions. The village of <location ref = "Maar Gan" visitable = "yes">Maar Gan</location> is the only sizable permanent <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location> settlement; <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, the district seat of <group ref = "House Redoran">House Redoran</group>, is on the margin of the region. <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s hunt for game here, and their herds find sparse grazing. It rains rarely, and suffers frequent ash storms.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Maar Gan" visitable = "yes">Maar Gan</location> is a small isolated village in a remote region north of <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location>. The <location ref = "Maar Gan" visitable = "yes">Maar Gan</location> shrine is an important Temple pilgrimage site.</p>
        
<p>        The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s Urshilaku tribe has a permanent settlement at <location ref = "Urshilaku camp" visitable = "yes">Urshilaku camp</location> in the <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location> region north of <location ref = "Maar Gan" visitable = "yes">Maar Gan</location> village.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location></p>
<p>        The rugged coast and islands of northern and eastern <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> are called <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location>. The region is rocky, infertile, and largely uninhabited, except for the outpost at Molag Mar, the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> settlements at <location ref = "Sadrith Mora" visitable = "yes">Sadrith Mora</location>, the wizard towers at <location ref = "Tel Aruhn" visitable = "yes">Tel Aruhn</location>, <location ref = "Tel Mora" visitable = "yes">Tel Mora</location>, and <location ref = "Tel Branora" visitable = "yes">Tel Branora</location>, and <location ref = "Ahemmusa camp" visitable = "yes">Ahemmusa camp</location> and the remote fishing villages of <location ref = "Ald Redaynia" visitable = "yes">Ald Redaynia</location> and <location ref = "Dagon Fel" visitable = "yes">Dagon Fel</location> on the north coast. There are no roads; most travel is by boat. Despite the rocky terrain, a variety of plants thrive on the regular rainfall.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Sadrith Mora" visitable = "yes">Sadrith Mora</location> is the district seat of House <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group>, and home of the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> Council, though only one <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> councilor actually lives in <location ref = "Sadrith Mora" visitable = "yes">Sadrith Mora</location>. <location ref = "Sadrith Mora" visitable = "yes">Sadrith Mora</location> is an island settlement, and accessible only by sea and teleportation. The town is large, with many services, but it is open only to <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> retainers; outsiders must confine themselves to the <location ref = "Gateway Inn" visitable = "yes">Gateway Inn</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Tel Branora" visitable = "yes">Tel Branora</location> is the tower and seat of the eccentric <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> wizard named Therana. The tower and its tiny village are located on a rocky promontory at the southeasternmost tip of <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Tel Fyr" visitable = "yes">Tel Fyr</location> is the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> tower of Sorcerer-Lord <person ref = "Divayth Fyr">Divayth Fyr</person>. Beneath the tower is the Corprusarium, a refuge-prison where the deranged, distorted victims of the deadly corprus disease are housed and tended.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Tel Aruhn" visitable = "yes">Tel Aruhn</location> is the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> tower of <person ref = "Arch-Mage Gothren">Arch-Mage Gothren</person>, <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> Sorcerer-Lord and head of the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> Council. The associated settlement is a sizable village, and the site of the Festival Slave Market, the largest slave market on <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Tel Mora" visitable = "yes">Tel Mora</location> is the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> tower of <person ref = "Mistress Dratha">Mistress Dratha</person>, an ancient wizard of the <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> Council. The small settlement includes a few craftsfolk and a tradehouse.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Tel Vos" visitable = "yes">Tel Vos</location> is the tower of <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> wizard and council member Master <person ref = "Aryon">Aryon</person>. <location ref = "Tel Vos" visitable = "yes">Tel Vos</location> is a peculiar blend of <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> and Western architectural styles, and is close to Vos village.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Bal Fell" visitable = "yes">Bal Fell</location> is the "City of Stone," an ancient First Era ruin in the southeastern islands and promontories of <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location>. The site has a nasty reputation, and several <group ref = "Telvanni">Telvanni</group> wizards currently have competing camps of hirelings and adventurers exploring and looting there. Legend says that <location ref = "Bal Fell" visitable = "yes">Bal Fell</location> was built on the site of an ancient Daedric worship center.</p>
        
<p>        The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group> Ahemmusa tribe has a permanent settlement at <location ref = "Ahemmusa camp" visitable = "yes">Ahemmusa camp</location> on a rocky promontory at the northeastern tip of the <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> mainland in the <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location> region.</p>
        
<p>        The <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location></p>
<p>        The western coast of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> from Seyda Neen north to <location ref = "Gnaar Mok" visitable = "yes">Gnaar Mok</location> is called the <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location>. The salt marshes and humid swamps of this region are uninhabited, with the only settlements found at the good harbors of <location ref = "Gnaar Mok" visitable = "yes">Gnaar Mok</location>, Hla Oad, and Seyda Neen. Also called the Smuggler's Coast, the region's secluded coves and islands provide refuge for criminal trade, and the frequent rain and fog hides small boats from Excise cutters.</p>
        
<p>        The piercing light of the Grand Pharos at the mouth of the harbor of the port village of Seyda Neen is a beacon to mariners throughout the <location ref = "Inner Sea" visitable = "yes">Inner Sea</location>. Most visitors from the Empire make landfall at the port of Seyda Neen, where they are processed by the Imperial Census and Excise Commission agents of the Coastguard station. The Coastguard cutters docked here control smuggling and piracy on the <location ref = "Inner Sea" visitable = "yes">Inner Sea</location>.</p>
        
<p>        Hla Oad is a tiny isolated fishing village on western <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> in the <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location> region. A rough track along the <location ref = "River Odai" visitable = "yes">River Odai</location> connects Hla Oad with the town of <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Gnaar Mok" visitable = "yes">Gnaar Mok</location> is a tiny island fishing village in the <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location> region of western <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>.</p>
        
<p>        The Grazelands</p>
<p>        The regular rain and dark soils of the Grazelands produce the rich grazing for <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group> herds that give the region its name. The region lies in the northeast of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>, sandwiched between the <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location> and <location ref = "Azura's Coast" visitable = "yes">Azura's Coast</location>. Permanent settlements include Vos village and the towers of <location ref = "Tel Vos" visitable = "yes">Tel Vos</location> and <location ref = "Tel Fyr" visitable = "yes">Tel Fyr</location>. The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s of Zainab camp move their herds across the plains in search of fresh grazing. There are no roads or tracks, but travel is easy across the open plains.</p>
        
<p>        The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group> Zainab tribe has a permanent settlement at Zainab camp, near the village of Vos in the Grazelands region.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location></p>
<p>        Located inland in the southeast of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>, <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location> is an uninhabited wasteland of rocky hills, steep-sided ravines, lava pools, and barren ash pavements. Pathfinding and travel is extremely difficult in this trackless wilderness, and is complicated by frequent ash storms. The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s of <location ref = "Erabenimsun camp" visitable = "yes">Erabenimsun camp</location> hunt game here, but few others venture into this region. The worst part of <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location>, called the <location ref = "Great Scathes" visitable = "yes">Great Scathes</location>, is considered impassible even by the <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s.</p>
        
<p>        The outpost at Molag Mar is a fortified stronghold on the southeastern edge of the desolate <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location> region. Pilgrims bound for the nearby pilgrimage sites at <location ref = "Mount Assarnibibi" visitable = "yes">Mount Assarnibibi</location> and <location ref = "Mount Kand" visitable = "yes">Mount Kand</location> take refuge at the outpost's hostels, comforted by the garrison of Redoran and <group ref = "Buoyant Armiger">Buoyant Armiger</group> crusaders stationed at the stronghold.</p>
        
<p>        The <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group> Erabenimsun tribe has a permanent settlement at <location ref = "Erabenimsun camp" visitable = "yes">Erabenimsun camp</location>, an isolated hut settlement in the middle of the desolate <location ref = "Molag Amur" visitable = "yes">Molag Amur</location> region.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location></p>
<p>        The dominant feature of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>, <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location>, is a vast volcano in the center of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>. The outer slopes are steep and rugged, and the crater is deep and dotted with surface lava. The Ghostfence, a magical barrier which blocks travel as well as seals in the harmful, disease-laden weather called 'blight,' rings the volcano's outer slopes, and is broken only at Ghostgate. Within the Ghostfence, rain never falls and the sun never shines; the only weather is the red and deadly ash-blight.</p>
        
<p>        Ghostgate is the gate citadel of the Ghostfence Ordinator and <group ref = "Buoyant Armiger">Buoyant Armiger</group> garrisons. Ghostgate sits astride the only gap through which the monstrous hosts of <person ref = "Dagoth Ur">Dagoth Ur</person> might emerge from <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location> to threaten the rest of <location ref = "Morrowind" visitable = "yes">Morrowind</location>. The Ghostfence itself is a colossal magical artifact that completely encircles <location ref = "Red Mountain" visitable = "yes">Red Mountain</location> and prevents the Blight from spilling its corruption across the rest of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>.</p>
        
<p>        West Gash</p>
<p>        The western highlands of Vvardefell are called the West Gash. The region extends from the <location ref = "Sea of Ghosts" visitable = "yes">Sea of Ghosts</location> on the northwest coast to the inland town of <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>, where the region is sandwiched between the <location ref = "Bitter Coast" visitable = "yes">Bitter Coast</location> and the <location ref = "Ashlands" visitable = "yes">Ashlands</location>. The trading village of <location ref = "Gnisis" visitable = "yes">Gnisis</location> is north of <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, and the fishing villages of Ald Veloth and <location ref = "Khuul" visitable = "yes">Khuul</location> lie on the north coast. The town of <location ref = "Caldera" visitable = "yes">Caldera</location> lies near <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>. The herds of the <group ref = "Ashlander">Ashlander</group>s of <location ref = "Urshilaku camp" visitable = "yes">Urshilaku camp</location> graze on the sparse but hardy highland vegetation.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location> is the district seat of <group ref = "House Hlaalu">House Hlaalu</group>, and the largest settlement on <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> after <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City. Good roads lead north to <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location> and south to <location ref = "Caldera" visitable = "yes">Caldera</location>, Seyda Neen, and <location ref = "Vivec" visitable = "yes">Vivec</location> City. The Imperial Legion garrison of <location ref = "Fort Moonmoth" visitable = "yes">Fort Moonmoth</location> lies south of <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Caldera" visitable = "yes">Caldera</location> is a recently chartered Imperial town and mining corporation. The <location ref = "Caldera" visitable = "yes">Caldera</location> Mining Company has been granted an Imperial monopoly to remove raw ebony from the rich deposits here. <location ref = "Caldera" visitable = "yes">Caldera</location> has the appearance and flavor of a Western Imperial town.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location> is the district seat of <group ref = "House Redoran">House Redoran</group>, and a large settlement. The <group ref = "Redoran Council Chamber">Redoran Council Chamber</group> are located inside the shell of an ancient extinct giant crab. Tracks lead north to <location ref = "Maar Gan" visitable = "yes">Maar Gan</location> and <location ref = "Gnisis" visitable = "yes">Gnisis</location> villages and south to <location ref = "Balmora" visitable = "yes">Balmora</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Gnisis" visitable = "yes">Gnisis</location> is a small mining and trade village astride the silt strider caravan route between the northwest West Gash and <location ref = "Ald'ruhn" visitable = "yes">Ald'ruhn</location>.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Ald Velothi" visitable = "yes">Ald Velothi</location> and <location ref = "Khuul" visitable = "yes">Khuul</location> are tiny fishing villages on the northern coast of the West Gash.</p>
        
<p>        <location ref = "Sheogorad" visitable = "yes">Sheogorad</location></p>
<p>        The large island of <location ref = "Sheogorad" visitable = "yes">Sheogorad</location> lies north of <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location>. This island and its associated lesser islands are a maritime wilderness extending north from <location ref = "Vvardenfell" visitable = "yes">Vvardenfell</location> into the <location ref = "Sea of Ghosts" visitable = "yes">Sea of Ghosts</location>. The region is largely hostile and uninhabited, with two small villages at <location ref = "Ald Redaynia" visitable = "yes">Ald Redaynia</location> and <location ref = "Dagon Fel" visitable = "yes">Dagon Fel</location>. Only <location ref = "Dagon Fel" visitable = "yes">Dagon Fel</location> is reached by ship services; all other island-to-island transport must be provided by the traveler.</p>
    </contents>
</Book>
