<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Honor Among Thieves">Honor Among Thieves</book_title>
    <writer who="Arnie the Scrib" listed="yes">Arnie the Scrib</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Ald'ruhn">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location ref="The Rat in the Pot">The Rat in the Pot</location>
        <location ref="Balmora">Balmora</location>, <location ref="South Wall Cornerclub">South Wall Cornerclub</location>
        <location ref="Vivec">Vivec</location>, <location ref="Simine Fralinie: Bookseller">Simine Fralinie: Bookseller</location>   
       
   </Acquisition>
    
    
    <contents>
        <p>Many admirers ask, "<person ref=">Arnie the Scrib">Arnie</person>, how can I become a flash and prosperous fellow like you?"</p>
        
        <p>And I tell them, "You want to join <group ref="Thieves Guild">the Guild</group>. Make friends. Be a part of something."</p>
        
        <p>"But who can join?" they ask.</p>
        
       <p> We're just like any other trade guild. We've got requirements. And if you want to advance in the ranks, we've got standards.</p>
        
        <p>You want to be fast and agile. You want to move undetected. You want to know about security -- locks, traps, and how to get around them. You want to defend yourself. You travel light and fast, and want light arms like <object><item ref="dagger">daggers</item></object> and <object><item ref="shortsword">shortswords</item></object>. You don't want to get into a slugging match, so you want the marksman's weapons
            -- the <object><item ref="bow">bow</item></object>, <object><item ref="crossbow">crossbow</item></object>, <object><item ref="throwing star">throwing star</item></object>, and <object><item ref="dart">dart</item></object>. You want <object><item ref="light armor">light armor</item></object>, so you can keep moving, and moving fast.</p>
        
        <p>Why belong? Simple. Everybody needs <group ref="Thieves Guild">friends</group>.</p>
        
        <p>The help of <group ref="Thieves Guild">friends</group> includes information. Your friends at the <group ref="Thieves Guild">Thieves Guild</group> know where the action is, and where the action is safe, and where it is not. The help of <group ref="Thieves Guild">friends</group> includes a place to rest, and a place to buy supplies and services -- training and tools. The help of friends includes fixing things with the guards at a discount rate. That's where the 'honor among thieves' part comes in. Friends stick together, and help each other.</p>
        
        <p>"But what about the competition?" my admirers ask.</p>
        
        <p>The competition is the <group ref="Camonna Tong">Camonna Tong</group>. And you don't want to join them, because they don't want you and they're not very nice. They have this thing about <group ref="outlanders">outlanders</group>. They want them all dead. So, unless your ambition is to be dead, you don't want to join them.</p>
        
        <p>And the <group ref="Camonna Tong">Camonna Tong</group> are bad people. The <group ref="Camonna Tong">Camonna Tong</group> don't mind killing people. Heck, they LIKE killing people. The <group ref="Thieves Guild">Thieves Guild</group>, on the other hand, thinks killing people is bad business. You want to be good people, right? So join the <group ref="Thieves Guild">Thieves Guild</group>, and stay far, far away from the <group ref="Camonna Tong">Camonna Tong</group>.</p>
        
        <p>So you want to join. But where do you look?</p>
        
        <p>Being a thief is not like being a fighter. You don't just go to the local guild Hall. The <group ref="Thieves Guild">Thieves Guild</group> doesn't have Guild Halls. But thieves like to be where their <group ref="Thieves Guild">friends</group> are. And where are their <group ref="Thieves Guild">friends</group>? At the local <location ref="South Wall Cornerclub" visitable="yes">cornerclub</location> or trade house. In <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location>, look for friends in <location ref="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>, <location ref="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location ref="Sadrith Mora" visitable="yes">Sadrith Mora</location>, and the <location ref="Foreign Quarter of Vivec" visitable="yes">Foreign Quarter of Vivec</location>.
   </p> 
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bk_honorthieves">bk_honorthieves</consoleID>
</Book>
