<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="RelaxNG_V2_morrowind.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title xmlid="Guide to Balmora">Guide to <location xmlid="Balmora" visitable="yes"
            >Balmora</location></book_title>
    <writer listed="no">
        <who xmlid="Anonymous">Anonymous</who>
    </writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Codus Callonus">Codus Callonus</who></NPC>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Dorisa Darvel">Dorisa Darvel</who></NPC>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Falvel Arenim"> Falvel Arenim </who></NPC>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Phane Rielle"> Phane Rielle </who></NPC>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Segunivus Mantedius"> Segunivus Mantedius </who></NPC>
        <NPC>
            <who xmlid="Sovor Trandel"> Sovor Trandel</who>
        </NPC> "random_book_imperial_dunmer" <item>(randomized item)</item>
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
        <line><location visitable="yes">Balmora</location> is the district seat of House Hlaalu, and the
        largest settlement on <location xmlid="Vvwardenfell" visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location> after <location
            xmlid = "Vivec City" visitable="yes">Vivec City</location>. <location xmlid="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>'s
        four districts are <location xmlid="High Town" visitable="yes">High Town</location>, the</line> <location
            xmlid="Commercial District" visitable="yes">Commercial District</location>, <location xmlid="Labor Town" visitable="yes">Labor
            Town</location>, and <location xmlid="Fort Moonmoth" visitable="yes">Fort Moonmoth</location>. <location
            xmlid="High Town" visitable="yes">High Town</location>, on the hill to the west, has the <location
            xmlid="Tribunal Temple" visitable="yes">Tribunal Temple</location>, <location xmlid="Hlaalu Council" visitable="yes">Hlaalu Council
                Hall</location>, rich manors, better shops, and the <location xmlid="Morag Tong guildhall" visitable="yes">Morag Tong
            guildhall</location>. <location xmlid="Commercial District" visitable="yes">The Commercial
                District, just west of the river, is centered on the large
        plaza north of South Gate, with the <location xmlid="strider port" visitable="yes">strider port along the south
            wall</location>, east of South Gate. The Fighters Guild and Mages Guild, and most of
            <location xmlid="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>'s shops and inns, are located along the
        streets of the <location xmlid="Commercial District" visitable="yes">Commercial District</location>. <location xmlid="Labor Town"
  visitable="yes">Labor Town</location>, east of the river, where the commoners and poor
        live, has several modest cornerclubs and a few merchants. <location xmlid="Fort Moonmoth" visitable="yes">Fort
            Moonmoth</location>, a long walk southeast of town, houses the Legion garrison and the
        Imperial cult. Services House Hlaalu services are available at <location xmlid="Hlaalu Council Manor" visitable="yes">Hlaalu Council Manor</location> in <location visitable="yes">High Town</location>.
        Temple faithful seek solace and services at the <location xmlid="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora
            Temple</location> in the southeast. Outlanders must travel outside the town walls,
        through South Gate and east along well-marked roads to <location xmlid="Fort Moonmoth" visitable="yes">Fort
            Moonmoth</location> for Imperial Legion and the Imperial cult services. The guildhalls
        of the Fighters Guild and Mages Guild are on the street north from the plaza in the
            <location xmlid="Commercial District" visitable="yes">Commercial District</location>. Morag Tong services are
        available at their guildhall in the extreme northwest of <location xmlid="High Town" visitable="yes">High Town</location>. Better shops are in <location xmlid="High Town" visitable="yes">High Town</location> on the hill, with numerous merchants in the
            <location xmlid="Commercial District" visitable="yes">Commercial District</location>, west of the river, and a few
        traders in <location xmlid="Labor Town" visitable="yes">Labor Town</location>, east of the river. Notable
        Figures None of the Hlaalu counselors live in <location xmlid="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>.
            <NPC who="Nileno Dorvayn"/> at the Council Hall is the ranking Hlaalu
        local. At the Fighters Guild, Eydis Fire-Eye is the steward. <NPC who="Ranis Athrys">Ranis
            Athrys</NPC> is the Mages Guild steward. <NPC who="Ethasi Rilvayn">Ethasi Rilvayn</NPC>
        is the Morag Tong steward. <NPC who="Feldrelo Sadri">Feldrelo Sadri</NPC> is the ranking
                cleric of the <location xmlid="Balmora Tribunal Temple" visitable="yes">Balmora Tribunal Temple</location>. The colorful
            <NPC who="'Sugar Lips' Habasi">'Sugar Lips' Habasi</NPC>, a freelance facilitator of no
        fixed address, is often rumored to be the local boss of the Thieves Guild. Transportation A
        good road leads south to <location xmlid="Pelagiad" visitable="yes">Pelagiad</location>, <location xmlid="Seyda Neen"
            visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location>, <location visitable="yes">Ebonheart</location>,
        and <location xmlid="Vivec" visitable="yes">Vivec</location>. A rugged wilderness track leads southwest
        along the Odai River to the fishing village of <location xmlid="Hla Oad" visitable="yes">Hla Oad</location>.
        Improved roads head north to Caldera and <location xmlid="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>. The
        silt strider port is on the west side of the river near South Gate. Silt strider service
        goes to <location xmlid="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location xmlid="Suran" visitable="yes"
            >Suran</location>, <location visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, and <location
            visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location>. Guild guides at the Mages Guild can teleport you
        to <location xmlid="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location xmlid="Vivec" visitable="yes"
        >Vivec</location>, <location xmlid="Caldera" visitable="yes">Caldera</location>, and <location xmlid="Sadrith Mora"
            visitable="yes">Sadrith Mora</location> for a fee. <location xmlid="Hla Oad" visitable="yes">Hla
            Oad</location> is southwest on the coast. An unimproved trail leads northeast up the
        ravines of <location xmlid="Foyada Mamaea" visitable="yes">Foyada Mamaea</location> to <location xmlid="Ghostgate" visitable="yes"
            >Ghostgate</location>; the path is easy to follow, but dangerous beasts threaten
        pilgrims who travel this route to <location xmlid="Ghostgate" visitable="yes">Ghostgate</location>
        shrine.</contents>
</Book>
