<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="file:/C:/Users/jerbe/OneDrive/Desktop/identityTransform/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book> 
    <book_title ref="msg_Dagoth">Message from Dagoth Ur</book_title>
    <writer who="Dagoth Ur" listed="yes"></writer>
    
    <Acquisition NPC="Dagoth Gares"> Dagoth Gares</Acquisition>
    
 
    <contents>
       <p> Lord <person who="Nerevar Indoril">Nerevar Indoril</person>, Hail <location ref="Resdaynia">Resdaynia</location> My Lord, Friend, and Companion
    </p>
  
  <p>  Once we were friends and
    brothers, Lord <person who="Nerevar Indoril">Nerevar</person>, in peace and in war. No houseman ever served you better, or more
    faithfully. Much that I did was at your command, at great cost to myself, and my honor. Yet
    beneath <location ref="Red Mountain">Red Mountain</location>, you struck me down as I guarded the <plot_device what="treasure">treasure</plot_device> you bound me by oath to
    defend. It was a cruel blow, a bitter betrayal, to be felled by your hand.</p>
    
  <p>  But, remembering our old friendship, I would forgive you, and raise you high in my service. The <group who="Sixth House">Sixth House</group> was not
    dead, but only sleeping. Now we wake from our long dream, coming forth to free <location ref="Morrowind">Morrowind</location> of
    foreign rulers and divine pretenders. When the land is swept clean of false friends and greedy
    thieves, the children of <person who="Veloth">Veloth</person> will build anew a garden of plenty in this <location ref="Morrowind">blighted wasteland</location>.
    Come to <location ref="Red Mountain">Red Mountain</location>, old friend. For the fellowship and honor that once we shared, I would
    grant you counsel and power, if only you would pledge that friendship anew. The path to <location ref="Red Mountain">Red
    Mountain</location> is long, and filled with danger, but if you are worthy, you will find there wisdom, a
    firm friend, and all the power you need to set the world aright. </p>
    
   <p> As ever, your respectful servant and loyal friend, 
    Lord <person who="Voryn Dagoth">Voryn Dagoth</person>, <person who="Dagoth Ur">Dagoth Ur</person> 
</p>
    </contents>

</Book>
