<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Book>
    
    <book_title ref =""></book_title>
    <writer who="Tal Marog Ker" listed ="yes">Tal Marog Ker</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref ="Tel Fyr, Hall of Fyr" visitable ="yes">Tel Fyr, Hall of Fyr</location>
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
        <p>Harvest's End, 3E 172</p>
        <p>Chimere, Master Sorcerer, Summoner, and <group ref="Direnni">Direnni</group> retainer.</p>
        <p><person ref="Chimere Graegyn">Chimere Graegyn</person> was a retainer of the ambitious <group ref="Direnni">Direnni</group> clan. The <group ref="Direnni">Direnni</group> derived the bulk of their power from their traffickings with <group ref="Daedra">Daedra</group>, a very profitable but risky path to success. Chimere was perhaps the cleverest and most ambitious of the <group ref="Direnni">Direnni</group> summoners. He dared to scheme against <person ref="Lord Dagon">Lord Dagonn</person>, and won. When his trick succeeded, Dagon was cast into <location ref ="Oblivion" visitable ="no">Oblivion</location>. However, in the instant of his betrayal, Dagon struck out against the mortal who tricked him. Chimere's pact assured that he would live forever in his home town among the happy voices of his friends and countrymen. Twisting the literal words of Chimere's pact, Dagon scooped up tiny <location ref ="Caecilly Island" visitable ="no">Caecilly Island</location> (a small island off the coast of Northmoor) and hurled in into the void. All Chimere's friends and countrymen were instantly killed, though the sounds of their voices remained to torment Chimere's memory. Chimere was condemned to live forever, to grow progressively old and crippled with arthritis, and to contemplate the tragic consequences of his defiance of fate and fortune in cheating a <group ref="Daedra">Daedra</group> Lord.</p>
        <p><object><item ref="Armor of the Saviour's Hide:">Armor of the Saviour's Hide:</item></object></p>
        <p>Created by the <group ref="Daedra">Daedra</group> Lord <person ref="Malacath">Malacath</person>, this armor has the marvelous property of turning the blow of an oathbreaker. Chimere tricked Dagon into swearing an oath against the Powers which he had no intention of keeping. The Hide of the Savior turned Dagon's titanic fury long enough for Chimere to deliver his own attack -- an incantation invoked upon Dagon's "Protonymic" (i.e., Incantory [sic] True Name). Unfortunately, like many of <person ref="Malacath">Malacath</person>'s gifts, the armor is a mixed blessing. It also makes its wearer exceptionally vulnerable to magical attacks, so one should only wear it for particular occasions.</p>
        <p>Dagon's Protonymic:</p>
        <p>Chimere used Dagon's Protonymic in an incantation to invoke a sorcery that would gradually drain all of Dagon's power into the void. Chimere miscalculated, however, not realizing that Dagon's resistance could slow the draining of his power, even if it could not stop it. As a result, Dagon had the time to curse Chimere with a literal fulfillment of the terms of his bargain with Chimere. Rather than let his power drain into the void, Dagon cast it all into his curse. As a result, <location ref ="Caecilly Island" visitable ="no">Caecilly Island</location> was cast into the void, all its citizens were horribly slain, and Chimere was condemned to live forever among the ruins of his greatest ambition.</p>
        <p>Rituals of the Hunt:</p>
        <p>The Chapel of the Innocent Quarry: Chimere believes that Dagon had <location ref ="Caecilly Island" visitable ="no">Caecilly Island</location> established as the site of the Chapel of the Innocent Quarry to personally mock and torment Chimere. The green crystal structure was created by enchantments, and is the only building on the island erected since it was ripped from <location ref ="Tamriel" visitable ="yes">Tamriel</location> and loosed in the void.</p>
        <p>The Spear:</p>
        <p>Supposedly the <object><item ref="Spear of Bitter Mercy">Spear of Bitter Mercy</item></object> used in the Wild Hunts could not be handled by any mortal or immortal save the ones sanctified to the Hunt and bound by its strictures. However, Chimere has determined that though the Spear's power is great, it is not unlimited, and that certain enchanted items -- for instance, the Armor of the Savior's Hide, forged by <person ref="Malacath">Malacath</person> -- are sufficient to protect a mortal or immortal bearer from its maleficent energies</p>
        
        
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bk_TalMarogKersResearches">bk_TalMarogKersResearches</consoleID>
</Book>                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 