<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../../Repository/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="The_Cantatas_of_Vivec">The Cantatas of Vivec</book_title>
    <writer listed="no">Anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>       
        <location ref="Balmora">Balmora</location>
        <location ref="Ebonheart">Ebonheart</location>
        <location ref="Gnisis">Gnisis</location>
        <location ref="Holamayan_Monastery">Holamayan Monastery</location>
        <location ref="Indarys_Manor">Indarys Manor</location>
        <location ref="Maar_Gan">Maar Gan</location>
        <location ref="Molag_Mar">Molag Mar</location>
        <location ref="Sadrith_Mora">Sadrith Mora</location>
        <location ref="Suran">Suran</location>
        <location ref="Tel_Branora">Tel Branora</location>
        <location ref="Tower_of_Tel_Fyr">Tower of Tel Fyr</location>
        <location ref="Tureynulal">Tureynulal</location>
        <location ref="Vivec City">Vivec City</location>        
        <location ref="Mournhold">Mournhold</location>
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
<p>        [The Cantatas of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> are gospels written in the form of epic songs. They trace the evolution of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> from a foolish mortal into an enlightened divine. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> sought out experiences that tested him in every way possible, particularly in the defense and protection of his <group ref="Dark_Elves">Dunmer</group> people, and through his long life, his humility, and his unconquerable spirit, he attained the Wisdom of the Seven Graces. The Cantatas relate many stories of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s experiments with challenge and risk, his failures and triumphs, his blessings of insight and good fortune, and his debt to his partners, <person ref="Almalexia">Almalexia</person> the Lover and <person ref="Sotha_Sil">Sotha Sil</person> the Teacher. The poetry is simple and dramatic, lyric and personal, composed to be sung or recited. The following is an excerpt from Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s 'Brooding Beneath <location ref="Red_Mountain" visitable="yes">Red Mountain</location>'.]</p>
        
       <p>The gaunt ghostfires loom as subtle shrouds,</p>
        
        <p>Smokes and shades on the biers of <location ref="Red_Mountain" visitable="yes">Red Mountain</location>.</p>
        
        
        <p>Arches and spires line the rock halls,</p>
        
        <p>Dimly lit by the spirits of the dead.</p>
        
        
        <p>The blood of broken hearths and houses</p>
        
        <p>Runs in red rivers, blossoms in fountains.</p>
        
        
        <p>Girdled round within walls of wit's glass</p>
        
        <p>The shattered hosts slumber in cradles of ash.</p>
        
        
        <p>But when shall they wake?</p>
        
        <p>What dark crucible may kindle their souls to light?</p>
        
        
        <p>How long beneath red-reeking clouds</p>
        
        <p>Must flickering watchfires burn?</p>
        
        
        <p>How many lifetimes of labor and lament</p>
        
        <p>Will it take to seal this restless tomb?</p>
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bk_CantatasOfVivec">bk_CantatasOfVivec</consoleID>
</Book>

