<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    
    <book_title ref ="Vivec_and_Mephala">Vivec and Mephala</book_title>
    <writer who="anonymous" listed ="yes">anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref ="Vivec,_Simine_Fralinie:_Bookseller" visitable ="yes">Vivec, Simine Fralinie: Bookseller</location>
        <location ref ="Mababi" visitable ="yes">Mababi</location>
        <location ref ="Balmora,_Dorisa_Darvel:_Bookseller" visitable ="yes">Balmora, Dorisa Darvel: Bookseller</location>
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
        
        <p>Who is <person ref="ALMSIVI">ALMSIVI</person>?</p>
        <p><location ref ="Morrowind" visitable ="yes">Morrowind</location> is holy country, and its gods are flesh and blood. Collectively, these gods are called the Tribunal, the triune <person ref="ALMSIVI">ALMSIVI</person>, three deities exemplifying <group ref="Dunmeri">Dunmeri</group> virtues. <person ref="Almalexial">Almalexia</person> is Mercy, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is Mastery, and <person ref="Sotha_Sil">Sotha Sil</person> is Mystery. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is easily the most popular of them all. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is also the most public, for he is the beloved Warrior-Poet of the True People, paradoxically beautiful and bloody. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is an artistic violence. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is represented in Temple literature and liturgy as one of the divine kings of <location ref ="Morrowind" visitable ="yes">Morrowind</location>. He guards the sacred <person ref="Velothi">Velothi</person> subcontinent of <location ref ="Vvardenfell" visitable ="yes">Vvardenfell</location>, and stands guard over <location ref ="Red Mountain" visitable ="yes">Red Mountain</location>, the gate to hell. He is part of the holy Tribunal, a god of the New Temple, and an aspect of the blessed and righteous <person ref="ALMSIVI">ALMSIVI</person>.</p>
        <p>This explicit presentation of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> the Guardian God-King and Warrior-Poet is the one most accessible and familiar to Westerners. However, it is important to remember that <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is also known to the Dunmer as the transcendent evolution of the <group ref="daedra">daedrai</group> that anticipated him, Black Hands Mephala, a foundation figure of the earliest <group ref="Chimer">Chimer</group>. This darker side of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> does not appear in the popular literature and liturgy, but is instinctively understood and accepted by the Dunmer as an integral part of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s divine aspect. A more complete appreciation of the complex nature of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> requires an understanding of the nature of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s Anticipation, Mephala, and the darker themes represented by this <group ref="daedra">daedrai</group> Lord's modes and motivations.</p>
        <p>Who is <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person>?</p>
        <p>Each of the three Tribunes of the Temple were represented in the dawn of <group ref="Chimer">Chimer</group>i culture by their Anticipations. These Anticipations are known to the West as the sinister <group ref="daedra">daedrai</group> Lords <person ref="Azura">Azura</person>, <person ref="Boethiah">Boethiah</person>, and <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person>. In Temple theology, however, <person ref="Azura">Azura</person> is the Anticipation of <person ref="Sotha_Sil">Sotha Sil</person>, the Mage-Lord of <person ref="ALMSIVI">ALMSIVI</person>. <person ref="Boethiah">Boethiah</person> is the Anticipation of <person ref="Almalexial">Almalexia</person>, <person ref="ALMSIVI">ALMSIVI</person>'s Mother and Lady. <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person> is the Anticipation of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>. According to legend, under the guidance of these three <group ref="daedra">daedrai</group> Lords, a discontented throng of <group ref="Altmer">Altmer</group> transformed themselves into a new people and founded a new land. And while <person ref="Boethiah">Boethiah</person>, the so-called Prince of Plots, provided the revolutionary methods needed to bring about this transformation, <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person> was the shadowy implementer of those methods.</p>
        <p>As known in the West, <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person> is the demon of murder, sex, and secrets. All of these themes contain subtle aspects and violent ones (assassination/genocide, courtship/orgy, tact/poetic truths); <person ref="Mephala">Mephala</person> is understood paradoxically to contain and integrate these contradictory themes. And all these subtle undercurrents and contradictions are present in the Dunmer concepts of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>, even if they are not explicitly described and explained in Temple doctrine.</p>
        <p>The Dunmer do not envision Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> as a creature of murder, sex, and secrets. Rather, they conceive of Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> as benevolent king, guardian warrior, poet-artist. But, at the same time, unconsciously, they accept the notion of darker, hidden currents beneath <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s benevolent aspects.</p>
        <p>For example, one of the most striking persistent myths associated with <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is the story that <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> conspired with his co-rulers <person ref="Almalexial">Almalexia</person> and <person ref="Sotha_Sil">Sotha Sil</person> in the murder of Lord <person ref="Nerevar">Nerevar</person>, the greatest of Dunmer heroes and generals. The story is derived from <group ref="Ashlander">Ashlander</group> oral tradition, and is flatly contradicted by all Temple traditions. Nonetheless, the tale is firmly established in the Dunmer imagination, as if to say, "Of course <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> would never have conspired to murder Lord <person ref="Nerevar">Nerevar</person>, but it happened so long ago... who can know the truth?"</p>
        <p>The public face of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> is benign, sensitive, compassionate, and protective of his followers. At the same time, the Dunmer seem irrationally comfortable with the hidden aspects of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>, the darker components of violence, lust, and conspiracy associated the more primitive and ruthless impulses of the Anticipations.</p>
        
        
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bk_vivecandmephala">bk_vivecandmephala</consoleID>
    
</Book>
