<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Arkay the Enemy">Arkay the Enemy</book_title>
    <writer who = "Mannimarco" listed = "yes">Mannimarco</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Scourg Burrow" visitable="yes">Scourg Burrow</location>
        

    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        
    <p>Hear me, children. Once I was a lowly man such as yourselves. By my will I entered the ranks
        of the <group ref = "gods">gods</group>. By your unquestioning devotion, you can share my glory.</p>

    <p>Most <group ref = "necromancers" >Necromancers</group> are fools and weaklings. Fodder for the <group ref = "witchhunters">witchhunters</group>. But you, my servants,
        you are among the chosen. In the days to come, few will dare to stand against your might.
        But one obstacle remains. His name is <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay</person>.</p>

    <p>He was also a man who entered the ranks of the <group ref = "gods">gods</group>. The similarities between his mortal life
        and my own astonish even me. It is only proper that we should be enemies.</p>

    <p><person ref = "Arkay">Arkay's</person> Blessing prevents the souls of men, <group ref = "beastmen">beastmen</group>, and <group ref = "elves">elves</group> from being used without
        consent. <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay's</person> Law prevents those buried with the proper rituals from being raised to
        serve my children's will. As you know, my children, <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay's</person> Blessing is flexible to those
        with daring, but <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay's</person> Law is unwavering.</p>

    <p>To the Scholars: Humiliate the priests of <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay</person>. Reveal the primitive burial customs to be
        mere superstition. Befriend kings with honeyed words and bind them to your will. Look to my
        children in <location ref = "Cyrodiil" visitable = "yes" >Cyrodiil</location> for guidance.</p>

    <p>To the Priests: Use your servants sparingly, let none be seen by the living. Let the memories
        of the undead waste away from the people. Send missionaries to the unbound dead, to the
        Vampires and the Liches. Let all the nations of dead carry my banner and my banner
        alone.</p>

    <p>To the Hidden: Wait, as always, in the darkness.</p>

    <p>For soon we shall strike. The Temples of <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay</person> will be torn stone from stone. The blood of
        his priests will sate our thirst; their bones will rise as our servants. The name <person ref = "Arkay">Arkay</person> will
        be stuck [sic] from the records. Only I shall hold sway over life and death. Only one name
        shall be whispered in fear. The name of your lord and master.</p>

    <p>KW</p>
    
    </contents>

</Book>
