<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Fighter's_Guild_Charter">Fighter's Guild Charter</book_title>
    <writer listed="no">Anonymous</writer>
    
<Acquisition>
    <location ref="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>, <location ref="Ald'ruhn Fighters Guild" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn Fighters Guild</location>
    <location ref="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>, <location ref="Balmora Fighters Guild" visitable="yes">Balmora Fighters Guild</location>
    <location ref="Sadright Mora" visitable="yes">Sadright Mora</location>, <location ref ="Wolverine Hall: Sadright Mora Fighters Guild" visitable="yes">Wolverine Hall: Sadrith Mora Fighters Guild</location>
    <location ref="Vivec City" visitable="yes">Vivec City</location>, <location ref="Vivec Fighters Guild" visitable="yes">Vivec Fighters Guild</location>
</Acquisition>
<contents>
<p>I. Purpose</p>
<p>
The <group ref="Guild of Fighters">Guild of Fighters</group> provides employment to free-swords and mercenaries and contracts to local citizens. Citizens may contract with the Guild for 
the removal of creatures and pests, the delivery of goods on dangerous routes, the collection of beasts for the arenas, and other duties defined by the
Guild Stewards.
</p>

<p>II. Authority</p>
<p>
The <group ref="Guild of Fighters">Guild of Fighters</group> was established under the section 4 of the "Guilds Act," and this charter was first confirmed under the Potentate <person ref="Versidue Shaie">Versidue Shaie</person>
in the 321st year of the Second Era.
</p>

<p>III. Rules and Procedures</p>
<p>
Any member of the <group ref="Guild of Fighters">Guild of Fighters</group> who strikes or steals from another member shall be expelled from the Guild. Re-admittance is at the discretion 
of the Guild Stewards.
</p>

<p>
Citizens who contract with the <group ref="Guild of Fighters">Guild of Fighters</group> and have a dispute may appeal first to the Guild Steward who accepted the contract and second with 
the authorities of each Province.
</p>

<p>IV. Membership Requirements</p>
<p>
The Guild selects candidates who are strong and healthy. A candidate must have some proficiency with long blades, axes, blunt weapons, 
and shields. Guildsmen must be able to use and maintain Heavy Armor.
</p>

<p>V. Applications for Membership</p>
<p>Candidates must present themselves to the <person ref="Steward of the Guild Hall">Steward of the Guild Hall</person> for examination and approval.
</p>
<p>ATTACHMENT A:</p>
<p>Fighters Guild Chapters in <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes">Vvardenfell District</location>, Province of Morrowind</p>

<p>Chapters are established in Guild-owned, free-standing guildhalls in the towns of <location ref="Ald'ruhn" visitable="yes">Ald'ruhn</location> and <location ref="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>. The chapter in <location ref="Sadright Mora" visitable="yes">Sadright Mora</location> is established in 
<location ref ="Wolverine Hall: Sadright Mora Fighters Guild" visitable="yes">Wolverine Hall: Sadrith Mora Fighters Guild</location> under lease from the <group ref="Telvanni Council">Telvanni Council</group>. The chapter in <location ref="Vivec City" visitable="yes">Vivec</location> is established in the Foreign Quarter under lease from the <location ref="yes" visitable="yes">Tribunal Temple</location>.</p>
</contents>
</Book>