<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Great Houses of Morrowind">Great Houses of Morrowind</book_title>
    <writer listed="no">Anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <person ref="Dorisa Darvel">Dorisa Darvel</person>
    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        <p>In modern times <location ref="Morrowind" visitable="yes">Morrowind</location> is ruled
            by five Great Houses: House <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group>, House <group
                ref="Redoran">Redoran</group>, House <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group>, House
                <group ref="Indoril">Indoril</group>, and House <group ref="Dres">Dres</group>. Only
            three of these Houses have interests in <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes"
                >Vvardenfell</location>. The three Great Houses on <location ref="Vvardenfell"
                visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location> identify themselves by their traditional
            colors: red for <group ref="Redoran">Redoran</group>, yellow for <group ref="Hlaalu"
                >Hlaalu</group>, and brown for <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group>. Thus, members
            of House <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> may be referred to collectively as
            Yellows.</p>

        <p>The Great Houses traditions derive from ancient <group ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group> clan
            and tribes, but now function as political parties. <group ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group>
            Great House membership is largely a matter of birth and marriage, but <group
                ref="Imperial">Imperial</group> colonists may also become retainers of a Great
            House, or may be adopted into a Great House. Initially an outlander may gain status in a
            house as an oath-bonded hireling, pledging exclusive loyalty to a single house and
            forsaking ambitions with all other houses. Later, after faithful service and advancement
            in lower ranks, an outlander may seek adoption into a Great House. Adoption and
            advancement to higher ranks in a Great House requires that a Great House councilor stand
            as sponsor for the candidate's character and loyalty. Finding a councilor to sponsor an
            outlander often involves performing a great service for the prospective sponsor.</p>

        <p>House <group ref="Redoran">Redoran</group> is one of the three <group ref="Dunmer"
                >Dunmer</group> Great Houses with holdings on <location ref="Vvardenfell"
                visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location>. The <group ref="Redoran">Redoran</group>
            prize the virtues of duty, gravity, and piety. Duty is to one's own honor, and to one's
            family and clan. Gravity is the essential seriousness of life. Life is hard, and events
            must be judged, endured, and reflected upon with due care and earnestness. Piety is
            respect for the gods, and the virtues they represent. A light, careless life is not
            worth living. <group ref="Redoran">Redoran</group> settlements are designed in the
                <group ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group> village style, built of local materials, with
            organic curves and undecorated exteriors inspired by the landscape and by the shells of
            giant native insects. <group ref="Redoran">Redoran</group> villages are typically
            centered on Temple compounds and their courtyards, with huts and tradehouses gathered
            around a central plaza, as in the West Gash village of <location ref="Gnisis"
                visitable="yes">Gnisis</location>. Ald'ruhn, the <group ref="Redoran"
                >Redoran</group> district seat, is exceptional, with its distinctive feature being
            the colossal prehistoric bug shell that has been adapted as the house's council
            house.</p>

        <p>As a result of its close relationship with the <group ref="Imperial">Imperial</group>
            administration, House <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> has emerged as politically and
            economically dominant among the Great Houses of <location ref="Vvardenfell"
                visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location> and <location ref="Morrowind" visitable="yes"
                >Morrowind</location>. <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> welcomes <group
                ref="Imperial">Imperial</group> culture and law, <group ref="Imperial"
                >Imperial</group> Legions and bureaucracy, and <group ref="Imperial"
                >Imperial</group> freedom of trade and religion. <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group>
            still honors the old <group ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group> ways—the ancestors, the Temple,
            and the noble houses—but has readily adapted to the rapid pace of change and progress in
            the <group ref="Imperial">Imperial</group> provinces. Unlike the other Great Houses,
            which are largely hostile to non-<group ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group>, House <group
                ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> aspires to live in peace and harmony with the other
            races, and to share in the growth and prosperity of the Empire. <group ref="Hlaalu"
                >Hlaalu</group> public buildings—tradehouses and craft guilds, manors and council
            halls—are designed as simple multi-storied buildings roughly rectangular in plan,
            featuring arched entranceways and modest decorated exteriors. More modest one-story
            private dwellings follow the same plan, except with less decoration. <group ref="Hlaalu"
                >Hlaalu</group> plantation estates resemble Temple compounds, with walled precincts
            enclosing outbuildings for craftsmen and servants, dominated by a grand manor residence
            in place of a Temple shrine.</p>

        <p>The wizard-lords of House <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group> have traditionally
            isolated themselves, pursuing wisdom and mastery in solitude. But certain ambitious
            wizards-lords, their retainers, and clients have entered whole-heartedly into the
            competition to control and exploit <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes"
                >Vvardenfell</location>'s land and resources, building towers and bases all along
            the eastern coast. According to <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group> principles, the
            powerful define the standards of virtue, and the <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group>
            are unwilling to allow the ambitious <group ref="Hlaalu">Hlaalu</group> to dominate
                <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location>'s untapped
            resources by default. <group ref="Telvanni">Telvanni</group> architecture is dominated
            by the wizards' tower, a fantastic organic form grown and sculpted from stems, caps, and
            root-like holdfasts of the giant native mushrooms. <group ref="Telvanni"
                >Telvanni</group> villages are comprised of smaller mushroom pods hollowed out for
            craftsmen and commoners. Open-air markets often include the giant cages displaying the
            wares of the slave masters.</p>

        <p>House <group ref="Indoril">Indoril</group> and House <group ref="Dres">Dres</group> are
            the two Great Houses without holdings or interest in <location ref="Vvardenfell"
                visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location>. <location ref="Indoril" visitable="yes"
                >Indoril</location> District occupies the heartland of <location ref="Morrowind"
                visitable="yes">Morrowind</location>, comprising the lands south of the Inner Sea
            and the eastern coast. The city of <location ref="Almalexia" visitable="yes"
                >Almalexia</location> is located in <location ref="Indoril" visitable="yes"
                >Indoril</location> District, and the <group ref="Indoril">Indoril</group> are
            orthodox and conservative supporters of the Temple and Temple authority. House <group
                ref="Indoril">Indoril</group> is openly hostile to <group ref="Imperial"
                >Imperial</group> culture and religion, and preserves many traditional <group
                ref="Dunmer">Dunmer</group> customs and practices in defiance of <group
                ref="Imperial">Imperial</group> law. <group ref="Dres">Dres</group> District is in
            the south of <location ref="Morrowind" visitable="yes">Morrowind</location>, bordering
            the swamps and marshes of Black Marsh. House <group ref="Dres">Dres</group> is an
            agrarian agricultural society, and its large saltrice plantations rely completely on
            slave labor for their economic viability. Always firm Temple supporters, House <group
                ref="Dres">Dres</group> is hostile to <group ref="Imperial">Imperial</group> law and
            culture, and in particular opposed to any attempts to limit the institution of
            slavery.</p>
    </contents>
</Book>
