<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Guide to Vivec">Guide to Vivec</book_title>
    <writer listed="no">Anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Vivec City, Hlaalu Treasury" visitable="yes">Vivec City, Hlaalu
            Treasury</location>
        <person ref="Codus Callonus">Codus Callonus</person>
        <person ref="Dorisa Darvel">Dorisa Darvel</person>
        <person ref="Elms Llervu">Elms Llervu</person>
        <person ref="Guldrise">Guldrise</person> Dralor <person ref="Iulus Truptor">Iulus
            Truptor</person>
        <person ref="Sevyni Saryon">Sevyni Saryon</person>
    </Acquisition>

    <contents>
        <p> Vivec is the largest settlement on <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes"
                >Vvardenfell</location>, and one of the largest cities in the East. Each of the
            great cantons is the size of a complete town. The <location ref="High Fane"
                visitable="yes">High Fane</location> and the <location ref="palace of Vivec"
                visitable="yes">palace of Vivec</location> are visited by hundreds of tourists and
            pilgrims daily. Citizens flock to the Arena for public entertainments like mock battles
            and comic plays. Outlanders mostly confine themselves to the <location
                ref="Foreign Canton" visitable="yes">Foreign Canton</location>, while natives live,
            work, and shop in the Great House compounds and residential cantons. But most of all,
            this is Lord Vivec's holy city. The <location ref="Ministry of Truth" visitable="yes"
                >Ministry of Truth</location>, the Temple prison, hangs above the great temple of
            the <location ref="High Fane" visitable="yes">High Fane</location>, the Halls of Wisdom
            and Justice, and Lord Vivec's Palace.</p>

        <p> Vivec is a city made up of eight cantons, each a little town in itself. On a map, it
            looks like a cross, with the Foreign Quarter at the top, the Temple Compound, with
            Vivec's Palace, the <location ref="High Fane" visitable="yes">High Fane</location>, the
                <location ref="Ministry of Truth" visitable="yes">Ministry of Truth</location>, and
            the <location ref="Hall of Wisdom" visitable="yes">Hall of Wisdom</location> and the
                <location ref="Hall of Justice" visitable="yes">Hall of Justice</location> at the
            bottom, the Hlaalu Compound to the west, the Telvanni Compound on the east, and four
            cantons grouped together at the center of the cross -- Redoran Compound northwest, Arena
            northeast, St. Delyn's Canton southwest, and St. Olms Canton southeast.</p>

        <p> The Foreign Quarter</p>
        <p> The Foreign Quarter is the large three-tiered canton to the north. Originally,
            foreigners were not allowed to enter Vivec any further than the Foreign Quarter, but now
            outlanders can travel throughout Vivec at will. The Imperial Guilds each have guildhalls
            and complete services here, and an Imperial cult shrine serves the spiritual needs of
            the Imperial faithful. Various independent tradesmen, craftsmen, and trainers also rent
            space here. The <location ref="Black Shalk Cornerclub" visitable="yes">Black Shalk
                Cornerclub</location> rents beds to non-guild visitors.</p>

        <p> Temple Compound</p>
        <p> The <location ref="High Fane" visitable="yes">High Fane</location> is the largest
            Tribunal temple on <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes">Vvardenfell</location>.
                <person ref="Archcanon Saryoni">Archcanon Saryoni</person> presides over the temple,
            along with a large staff of priests, healers, and monks. Pilgrims travel from all over
            Morrowind to view the <location ref="High Fane" visitable="yes">High Fane</location> and
            the <location ref="Ministry of Truth" visitable="yes">Ministry of Truth</location>, and
            to offer prayer and thanks before the <location ref="Palace of Vivec" visitable="yes"
                >Palace of Vivec</location>. The <location ref="Ministry of Truth" visitable="yes"
                >Ministry of Truth</location>, a celestial body suspended by <person ref="Vivec"
                >Vivec</person>'s mighty power over the Temple Compound, is the headquarters of the
            Temple Ordinators, and heretics are imprisoned and re-educated there. The <location
                ref="Hall of Wisdom" visitable="yes">Hall of Wisdom</location> and <location
                ref="Hall of Justice" visitable="yes">Hall of Justice</location> contain the
            executive, administrative, judicial, and martial operations of the Tribunal Temple. The
                <location ref="Palace of Vivec" visitable="yes">Palace of Vivec</location> is the
            abode of the god-hero Lord Vivec, the Warrior-Poet of the three deities who comprise
                <group ref="Almsivi">Almsivi</group>, the divine patrons of the Tribunal Temple.
            Only the most devout are admitted to the presence of Lord <person ref="Vivec"
                >Vivec</person>, and only at his initiation. Beneath the <location
                ref="Palace of Vivec" visitable="yes">Palace of Vivec</location> is the <location
                ref="Puzzle Canal" visitable="yes">Puzzle Canal</location>, a place of worship and
            testing for questing heroes hoping to receive <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s
            favor. Many choice treasures are guarded by Daedric servants in the <location
                ref="Puzzle Canal" visitable="yes">Puzzle Canal</location>'s dark passages.</p>

        <p> Hlaalu Compound</p>
        <p> Hlaalu Compound is the westmost canton. The Hlaalu Councilor <person
                ref="Crassius Curio">Crassius Curio</person> has a splendid tier-top mansion here.
            The tiers below contain Hlaalu treasuries, records, holding cells, and various Great
            House services. There are two public houses: the <group ref="Elven Nations">Elven
                Nations</group> and the <group ref="No Name Club">No Name Club</group>. A variety of
            craftsmen and tradesmen also have shops at Hlaalu Compound. Some House Hlaalu nobles and
            retainers prefer to maintain their residences in the less-formal St. Delyn and St. Olms
            cantons.</p>

        <p> Telvanni Compound</p>
        <p> Telvanni Compound is the eastmost canton. The mage-lord <person ref="Mavon Drenim">Mavon
                Drenim</person> is the ranking Telvanni noble. The Telvanni rent the compound from
            the Temple, and have to make do with a Velothi tower instead of their preferred mushroom
            towers. The administrative center includes a treasury and a hall of records. Slaves are
            housed in the lowest tiers, along with cells full of monsters. There are many tradesmen,
            craftsmen, and trainers, and <location ref="the Lizard's Head" visitable="yes">the
                Lizard's Head</location> cornerclub provides lodgings for Telvanni kin and
            mercenaries.</p>

        <p> Redoran Compound</p>
        <p> Redoran Compound is the canton south of the Foreign Quarter, west of and next to the
            Arena. The Redoran administrative center there includes the <location
                ref="Redoran Treasury" visitable="yes">Redoran Treasury</location>, <location
                ref="Hall of Records" visitable="yes">Hall of Records</location>, and <location
                ref="Holding Cells" visitable="yes">Holding Cells</location>. On the lowest tier is
            a Redoran shrine and ancestral vaults. Two noble families, the Savens and the Dralors,
            have top-tier manors. There are many tradesmen, craftsmen, and trainers, and the
                <location ref="Flowers of Gold" visitable="yes">Flowers of Gold</location>
            cornerclub provides lodgings for Redoran kin and retainers.</p>

        <p> Arena Compound</p>
        <p> The Arena Compound lies between the Redoran compound on the west and the Telvanni
            compound on the east. The Arena is the site of public entertainments and combat sports.
            The comfortable domed Arena has seating for hundreds of spectators; beneath the Arena
            are dressing and storage rooms for entertainers and training rooms and animal pens for
            the combat competitors.</p>

        <p> St. Delyn and St. Olms Residential Cantons</p>
        <p> St. Delyn Canton and St. Olms Canton are residence cantons for commoners and paupers.
            The Temple charges very reasonable rents for comfortable workshops, shops, and
            apartments, and most of <location ref="Vvardenfell" visitable="yes"
                >Vvardenfell</location>'s crafts and light industry are housed in these cantons.
                <location ref="The Abbey of St. Delyn the Wise" visitable="yes">The Abbey of St.
                Delyn the Wise</location> is on the top tier of St. Delyn, and Hlaalu Councilor
                <person ref="Yngling Half-Troll">Yngling Half-Troll</person> has a top-tier manor on
            St. Olms.</p>

        <p> Transportation</p>
        <p> Foot bridges connect with the mainland between the <location ref="Ebonheart"
                visitable="yes">Ebonheart</location> region and Hlaalu Compound, between the north
            bay region and the Foreign Quarter, and between the east bay region and Telvanni
            Compound. Good roads lead from the Hlaalu Compound bridge south to <location
                ref="Ebonheart" visitable="yes">Ebonheart</location> and north to <location
                ref="Seyda Neen" visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location> and points north. Good roads
            lead from the Foreign Quarter bridge west towards <location ref="Seyda Neen"
                visitable="yes">Seyda Neen</location>, north towards <location ref="Suran"
                visitable="yes">Suran</location> and the <location ref="Ascadian Isles"
                visitable="yes">Ascadian Isles</location>, and east towards <location
                ref="Molag Mar" visitable="yes">Molag Mar</location>. Roads from the Telvanni
            Compound bridge are useful mostly for travelers to <location ref="Molag Mar"
                visitable="yes">Molag Mar</location>. Silt strider service is available at the north
            end of the Foreign Quarter bridge, traveling from Vivec to <location ref="Suran"
                visitable="yes">Suran</location>, <location ref="Seyda Neen" visitable="yes">Seyda
                Neen</location>, <location ref="Balmora" visitable="yes">Balmora</location>, and
                <location ref="Molag Mar" visitable="yes">Molag Mar</location>. Ships from the docks
            at the Foreign Quarter travel to <location ref="Ebonheart" visitable="yes"
                >Ebonheart</location>, <location ref="Hla Oad" visitable="yes">Hla Oad</location>,
                <location ref="Molag Mar" visitable="yes">Molag Mar</location>, and <location
                ref="Tel Branora" visitable="yes">Tel Branora</location>. Ships from nearby
                <location ref="Ebonheart" visitable="yes">Ebonheart</location> sail to <location
                ref="Hla Oad" visitable="yes">Hla Oad</location>, Sadrith Mora, <location
                ref="Tel Branora" visitable="yes">Tel Branora</location>, and the Foreign Quarter of
                <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>. Low-fare gondolas shuttle passengers from canton
            to canton via Vivec's canals.</p>
    </contents>
</Book>
