<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="GitHub/Elder_Scrolls/xml/Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    
    <book_title ref ="The_Prayers_of_Baranat">The Prayers of Baranat</book_title>
    <writer who="anonymous" listed ="yes">anonymous</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref ="Ald'ruhn,-Morag_Tong_Guildhall" visitable ="yes">Ald'ruhn, Morag Tong Guildhall</location>
        <location ref ="Punammu" visitable ="yes">Punammu</location>
        <location ref ="Sethan_Ancestral_Tomb" visitable ="yes">Sethan Ancestral Tomb</location>
        
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
        
        <p>When the Lady <person ref="Genevrah">Genevrah</person> was kidnapped from her estate and held for ransom, her mother sent word out that whoever rescued her would be allowed to marry her and inherit the land. Unfortunately, in those troubled days, kidnappings, murders, and thievery were rampant, and there was a dearth of able-bodied adventurers for such assignments. In fact, the only person who answered her call was a skinny, little fellow named <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>.</p>
        <p>"You are certainly brave, but I fear you would never survive," said the old woman. "My daughter, you see, has been kidnapped by the Coribael brothers whose physical prowess is the stuff of legend."</p>
        <p>"My lady," said <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>. "When I was born, I was blessed by <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>, <person ref="Almalexia">Almalexia</person>, and <person ref="Sotha_Sil">Sotha Sil</person>, and I have the ear of the saints. If I run into any trouble, I'll call on them to aid my quest."</p>
        <p>Doubtful, but having no other prospects, the old woman sent <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> off, explaining that the four brothers' camp was to the north. In the center of the camp, the eldest and most powerful brother <person ref="Airen_Coribaell">Airen Coribael</person> was holding Lady <person ref="Genevrah">Genevrah</person> personally. Each of his brothers guarded a different post along the valley -- <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> would have to defeat each to rescue the lady.</p>
        <p><person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> rode many miles through the northern swamps before he came to the first of the brothers' guard posts. There he saw <person ref="Vanis_Coribael">Vanis Coribael</person>, the youngest of the brothers, watching the valley for intruders. Vanis was known to be faster than the wind, a warrior who could thrash his opponents before they even unsheathed their weapons. <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> look a look at his sad, cut-rate iron blade, and prayed to the saints.</p>
        <p>Saint <person ref="Veloth">Veloth</person> the Pilgrim appeared before <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> in shining robes, and smiled upon him, "<person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>, put down your blade and I will make you swifter than bolt of lightning."</p>
        <p><person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> dropped his blade and ran at Vanis, moving so fast he didn't rustle a leaf with his pace. In a flash, Vanis was dead by <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>'s hands. The adventurer continued on until he reached the second youngest Coribael brother, Feryn, who not only was as fast as Vanis, but so strong, he could rip a <object><item ref="trama_shrub"></item>trama shrub</object> up by the roots with two fingers. <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> hid himself and trembled as he looked at the <group ref="giant">giant</group> Feryn Coribael. Again, the young adventurer prayed to the saints.</p>
        <p>Saint Nerevar the Captain appeared before <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> in golden armor, and smiled upon him, "<person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>, I will make you stronger than a hundred warriors."</p>
        <p><person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> rushed at Feryn, knocking the <group ref="giant">giant</group> through a boulder which turned to dust on impact. Feryn tried to get to his feet, but <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> tore him apart, scattering him across the valley floor in eighty-seven pieces. Beyond Feryn's post was a raging river, where the second eldest Coribael brother, Horis, stood guard. Horis, who was faster than his brother Vanis, stronger than his brother Feryn, and so tough that he could swim in the lava of <location ref ="Dagoth_Ur" visitable ="yes">Dagoth Ur</location> like it was the <location ref ="Padomaic_Ocean" visitable ="yes">Padomaic Ocean</location>. <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> thought of his own tolerance for pain, which was minimal, and prayed to the saints for help.</p>
        <p>Saint <person ref="Roris">Roris</person> the Martyr appeared before <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> with flesh like sparkling gems, and smiled on him, "<person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>, I will make you unyielding as the heart of <location ref ="Oblivion" visitable ="no">Oblivion</location>."</p>
        <p><person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> rushed at Horis, and two plunged into the rushing river. For twelve hours, they wrestled one another under the water, until Horis could hold his breath no more and drowned. <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> pulled himself out of the river and continued down the valley, until he reached the camp. <person ref="Airen_Coribaell">Airen Coribael</person> himself was there, guarding a squirming sack which <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> assumed either contained Lady <person ref="Genevrah">Genevrah</person> or several large cats. The young adventurer quailed at the prospect of doing battle with <person ref="Airen_Coribaell">Airen Coribael</person>, the swiftest, strongest, sturdiest, and most accomplished fighter of the brothers. He prayed to the saints for help.</p>
        <p>Saint <person ref="Olms">Olms</person> the Just appeared before <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> in a burst of flame, and smiled on him, "<person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>, I will make you more cunning in battle than the most dangerous of <group ref="daedra">daedra</group>."</p>
        <p><person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> walked calmly into the camp and began battle with <person ref="Airen_Coribaell">Airen Coribael</person>. The fight lasted seven days, and for six of them, Airen had the upper hand. He rained kicks and punches down using the arrhythmic style the <group ref="Khajiit">Khajiit</group> call <person ref="Goutfang">Goutfang</person>; he parried and blocked in all the fashions of the great <group ref="Nordic">Nordic</group> warriors; he maintained his balance, coordination, speed, strength, timing, and tactics as the moons rose and fell from the sky. But on the seventh day, as he was preparing his Killing Blow, he suddenly stopped, eyes wide open. The blood drained from his face, and he realized the trap he had stepped into. A trap with no escape. With three quick flashes of his hand, <person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person> completed the Cycle of Blood, the old <group ref="Redguard">Redguard</group> fighting style he had begun on day one. <person ref="Airen_Coribaell">Airen Coribael</person> breathed no more.</p>
        <p>The young adventurer ran to open the sack where Lady <person ref="Genevrah">Genevrah</person> lay. His first surprise. She had a face like a <group ref="dreugh">dreugh</group> and as she began to berate him for taking his time, he realized that she had a very, very, very unpleasant personality as well. Several days later, when they were back at the old woman's court, he discovered that the estate that he would be inheriting was utterly dissolute by decades of blight storms and poor crops.</p>
        <p>Saint <person ref="Delyn">Delyn</person> the Wise watched the young adventurer from a cloud in the sky, and smiled on him, "<person ref="Baranat">Baranat</person>, before you fight, find out what you're fighting for."</p>
        
        
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bookskill_hand to hand1">bookskill_hand to hand1</consoleID>
    
</Book>
