<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    
    <book_title ref ="The_Pilgrim's_Path">The Pilgrim's Path</book_title>
    <writer who="Tribunal_Temple" listed ="yes">Tribunal Temple</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref ="Fields_of_Kummu" visitable ="yes">Fields of Kummu</location>
        <location ref ="Ghostgate" visitable ="yes">Ghostgate</location>
        <location ref ="Gnisis" visitable ="yes">Gnisis</location>
        <location ref ="Koal_Cave" visitable ="yes">Koal Cave</location>
        <location ref ="Vivec" visitable ="yes">Vivec</location>
        
    </Acquisition>
    <contents>
        
        <p>The pilgrim must visit each of the <location ref ="Shrines_of_the_Seven_Graces" visitable ="yes">Shrines of the Seven Graces</location>. At each site the pilgrim must stand before the three-sided stone triolith and read the inscription. To ease the pilgrim's task, the <group ref="Temple">Temple </group> has made this list of shrines along with directions and advice to pilgrims. The blessings of each shrine last at least a half day.</p>
        <p>The <location ref ="Fields_of_Kummu" visitable ="yes">Fields of Kummu</location>: Shrine of Humility</p>
        <p>Here Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> met a poor farmer whose <object><item ref="guar">guar</item></object> had died. The farmer could not harvest his <object><item ref="muck">muck</item></object> without his <object><item ref="guar">guar</item></object>, and he could not provide for his family or his village. So the Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> removed his fine clothes and toiled in the fields like a beast of burden until the crop was harvested. It is at the <location ref ="Fields_of_Kummu" visitable ="yes">Fields of Kummu</location> we go to pray for the same humility Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> showed on that day.</p>
        <p>The <location ref ="Fields_of_Kummu" visitable ="yes">Fields of Kummu</location> are west of <location ref ="Suran" visitable ="yes">Suran</location> on the north shore of <location ref ="Lake_Amaya" visitable ="yes">Lake Amaya</location> as you head towards <location ref ="Pelagiad" visitable ="yes">Pelagiad</location>. The shrine is between two rocks, and most easily noticed while traveling east along the road. <person ref="Alof">Alof</person>'s farm nearby has a small dock on the north bank of <location ref ="Lake_Amaya" visitable ="yes">Lake Amaya</location>. This is the only dock nearby which <person ref="Alof">Alof</person> kindly allows servants of the <group ref="Temple">Temple </group> to use. It is customary to leave a portion of <object><item ref="muck">muck</item></object> at the shrine to represent <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s humility.</p>
        <p>To Stop the Moon: The Shrine of Daring</p>
        <p>When Sheogorath rebelled against the Tribunal, he tricked the moon Baar Dau into forsaking its appointed path through <location ref ="Oblivion" visitable ="no">Oblivion</location>. The Mad Star inspired the moon to hurl itself upon <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s new city, which Sheogorath claimed was built in mockery of the heavens. When <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> learned of Sheogorath's scheme, he froze the rogue moon in the sky with a single gesture and the grace of his countenance. Overwhelmed by the courage and daring of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>, the moon Baar Dau swore itself to eternal service of the Tribunal and all its works. Thus the moon now stands guard over the palace, and serves as a citadel for the <group ref="Temple">Temple </group>'s Ordinators.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Daring is found in the city of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>, in the <location ref ="Temple_District" visitable ="yes">Temple District</location>, along the western wall of the <location ref ="High_Fane" visitable ="yes">High Fane</location>, the great Temple of <location ref ="Vvardenfell" visitable ="no">Vvardenfell</location>. When you address the shrine, it is customary to leave behind a Potion of Rising Force. Suitable potions may be purchased from the <group ref="Temple">Temple </group>. Homemade potions are not acceptable.</p>
        <p>The Palace: Shrine of Generosity</p>
        <p>Long after Lord <person ref="Nerevar">Nerevar</person> and the <group ref="Tribunal">Tribunal</group> triumphed over <person ref="Dagoth_Ur">Dagoth Ur</person>, the people wished to build a monument to the heroes of that war. Vivec thanked them, but said that it would be better to dedicate a monument not only to the glorious heroes, but to all people, great and small, who suffered and died in the war. It became the custom to make offerings here, either in thanks of our good fortune, or for those less fortunate.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Generosity is on the top steps of Vivec's Palace, the southernmost Canton of Vivec City. The customary donation for those in good fortune is 100 gold.</p>
        <p>In a battle with <person ref="Mehrunes_Dagon">Mehrunes Dagon</person>, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> gave his own silver longsword to the <group ref="Daedra">Daedra</group> Lord rather than dishonor himself by fighting an unarmed foe. This so impressed the <group ref="Dremora">Dremora</group>, the most honorable and chivalrous of <person ref="Mehrunes_Dagon">Mehrunes Dagon</person>'s Daedric servants, that they now share a bond of respect and courtesy with the followers of the <group ref="Tribunal">Tribunal</group>, though we must never forget that they are our enemies.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Courtesy is found in the heart of the <location ref ="Puzzle_Canal" visitable ="yes">Puzzle Canal</location>, a labyrinth beneath Lord <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s Palace in the city of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>. The journey though the <location ref ="Puzzle_Canal" visitable ="yes">Puzzle Canal</location> can be confusing and it is suggested that common pilgrims carry a scroll of ALMSIVI Intervention in case they get lost. The <group ref="Dremora">Dremora</group> <person ref="Krazzt">Krazzt</person> is found in the center of the <location ref ="Puzzle_Canal" visitable ="yes">Puzzle Canal</location>, and will accept a plain silver longsword if spoken to with courtesy. After <person ref="Krazzt">Krazzt</person> accepts the sword, pilgrims must read the inscription on the triolith.</p>
        <p>The Mask of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>: Shrine of Justice</p>
        <p>Near the altar is <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s Ash Mask. In the Days of Fire when <person ref="Dagoth_Ur">Dagoth Ur</person> first crept back into <location ref ="Red_Mountain" visitable ="yes">Red Mountain</location> and awakened it, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> led refugees here as they fled the ash and blight. Weary, they rested here a while. When <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> awoke, he found himself and all his followers encased in casts of grey ash. Frozen like a sleeping statue and unable to free himself or help his people, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> was filled with despair. <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s tears weakened his ash cast. He tore the ash from his perished followers, breathed life into their lungs, and cured them of the blight. This is <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s heroism -- his tender heart provides strength when his might fails.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Justice is guarded within the <location ref ="Gnisis" visitable ="yes">Gnisis</location> Temple, in the village of <location ref ="Gnisis" visitable ="yes">Gnisis</location>, northwest by road from the town of <location ref ="Ald'ruhn" visitable ="yes">Ald'ruhn</location>. When you address the shrine, it is customary to leave a potion of <object><item ref="Cure_Common_Disease">Cure Common Disease</item></object> as a token of your respect for justice. Suitable potions may be purchased from Temple. Homemade potions are not acceptable.</p>
        <p><location ref ="Koal_Cave" visitable ="yes">Koal Cave</location>: The Shrine of Valor</p>
        <p>Within the <location ref ="Koal_Cave" visitable ="yes">Koal Cave</location>, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> fought a battle with <person ref="Ruddy_Man">Ruddy Man</person>, the father of the <group ref="Dreugh">Dreugh</group>. When he defeated <person ref="Ruddy_Man">Ruddy Man</person>, <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person> spared his life, on the condition that <person ref="Ruddy_Man">Ruddy Man</person> and his children would give up their tough hides to serve as armor for the Dunmer.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Valor is inside the <location ref ="Koal_Cave" visitable ="yes">Koal Cave</location>, a cavern on the seacoast west of the ancient stronghold <location ref ="Berandas" visitable ="yes">Berandas</location> and south of <location ref ="Gnisis" visitable ="yes">Gnisis</location>. The cave mouth faces south, towards the sea, and is marked by a large natural arch of stone. The region is wilderness, and finding the cave mouth can be difficult. <group ref="Dreugh">Dreugh</group> within the cave itself are fearsome enemies; only experienced and capable adventurers should attempt to re-enact the epic battle with the <group ref="Dreugh">Dreugh</group> in the cave. <group ref="Dreugh">Dreugh</group> wax may be bought at the Temple in <location ref ="Gnisis" visitable ="yes">Gnisis</location>. When you address the shrine, it is customary to leave a portion of <object><item ref="dreugh_wax">dreugh wax</item></object> as a token of <person ref="Vivec">Vivec</person>'s victorious struggle with <person ref="Ruddy_Man">Ruddy Man</person>.</p>
        <p>The <location ref ="Ghostfence" visitable ="yes">Ghostfence</location>: The Shrine of Pride</p>
        <p>The <location ref ="Ghostfence" visitable ="yes">Ghostfence</location> is a lasting symbol of the indomitable will and power of ALMSIVI, and a monument to Dunmer pride in overcoming its enemies.</p>
        <p>The Shrine of Pride is found within the <location ref ="Ghostfence" visitable ="yes">Ghostfence</location>, just northeast of the <location ref ="Ghostgate" visitable ="yes">Ghostgate</location> itself. The safest route to <location ref ="Ghostgate" visitable ="yes">Ghostgate</location> is along the <location ref ="Foyada_Mamaea" visitable ="yes">Foyada Mamaea</location>, a volcanic ravine running from the top of <location ref ="Red_Mountain" visitable ="yes">Red Mountain</location> southwest to its end just below <location ref ="Balmora" visitable ="yes">Balmora</location>. An old <group ref="Dwemer">Dwemer</group> bridge crosses the foyada near <location ref ="Fort_Moonmoth" visitable ="yes">Fort Moonmoth</location>. A pilgrim may follow the <location ref ="Foyada_Mamaea" visitable ="yes">Foyada Mamaea</location> all the way to <location ref ="Ghostgate" visitable ="yes">Ghostgate</location>. Any journey inside the <location ref ="Ghostfence" visitable ="yes">Ghostfence</location> is dangerous, but even the most timid pilgrim should be safe, so long as he does not stray too far from the <location ref ="Ghostgate" visitable ="yes">Ghostgate</location> and flees from any minions of <person ref="Dagoth_Ur">Dagoth Ur</person>. When you address the shrine, it is customary to leave a <object><item ref="soul_gem">soul gem</item></object> in remembrance of our ancestors who were bound to the <group ref="Tribunal">Tribunal</group>'s service.</p>
        
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bk_PilgrimsPath">bk_PilgrimsPath</consoleID>
</Book>
