<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="Schema/morrowindBookSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<Book>
    <book_title ref="Silence">Silence</book_title>
    <writer who="Ganpheril Kimeth" listed="yes">Ganpheril Kimeth</writer>
    <Acquisition>
        <location ref="Endusal" visitable="yes">Endusal</location>, <location ref="Kagrenac's Study"
            visitable="yes">Kagrenac's Study</location>
        <location ref="Urshilaku" visitable="yes">Urshilaku</location>, <location
            ref="Laterus Burial" visitable="yes">Laterus Burial</location>
    </Acquisition>


    <contents>
        <p>Silence</p>
        <p>by <person ref="Ganpheril Kimeth">Ganpheril Kimeth</person></p>
        <p>“I've heard of you,” said the old vagabond, very impressed. “Aren't you the adventurer
            who slew all those ash vampires in <location ref="Ghostgate">Ghostgate</location> a
            couple of months back?”</p>

        <p>“That I am,” said <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Oristian Silverthorn</person> with a
            weary smile for his admirer. He knew that his name was not yet legendary, and it was
            best to be polite. “And you are?”</p>

        <p>“My name would have no meaning to you, but I'm <person ref="Erer Darothil">Erer
                Darothil</person>,” he said, raising a glass of <object><item ref="Greef"
                    >greef</item></object>. “I hail from the region of <location ref="Ghostgate"
                >Ghostgate</location> which is how I heard your name. Are you on an adventure as we
            speak?”</p>

        <p>“Yes,” said <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person>, with a grim
            expression. “I'm challenged to rid The <location ref="Grazelands" visitable="yes"
                >Grazelands</location> of a rogue battlemage by the name of <person ref="Egroamaro"
                >Egroamaro</person>.”</p>

        <p>“I've heard of him as well,” said <person ref="Erer Darothil">Darothil</person>. “He is
            said to be very powerful, an implacable foe.”</p>

        <p>“That is why I'm drinking now,” sighed <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn"
                >Silverthorn</person>. “So tell me, what is your profession?”</p>

        <p>“I do nothing,” said <person ref="Erer Darothil">Darothil</person> with some measure of
            pride. “But in my youth, I used to teach the skills of Illusion at the <location
                ref="University of Gwylim" visitable="no">University of Gwylim</location>.”</p>

        <p>“Perhaps you can help me then,” said <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn"
                >Silverthorn</person>, suddenly excited. “Can you teach the spell Silence? I can
            certainly pay you.”</p>

        <p>“I know that spell,” said <person ref="Erer Darothil">Darothil</person>. “You might find
            Invisibility very helpful as well, or perhaps Darkness which would allow you to sneak up
            on old <person ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person>.”</p>

        <p>“No,” said <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person> firmly. “I only have
            time to learn one spell. I have to kill <person ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person>,
            collect the award, and be back in <location ref="Gnisis" visitable="yes"
                >Gnisis</location> as quickly as possible. My wife worries when I'm away.”</p>

        <p><person ref="Erer Darothil">Darothil</person> agreed and, as the two settled back in
            their seats at the cornerclub and tossed back glasses of <object><item ref="Greef"
                    >greef</item></object>, the old man shared his knowledge of the spell. He
            explained what it truly meant to bend sound, creating a cone of silence as glass can
            bend light. He had <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person> close his
            eyes while he tapped the side of his glass, making him picture the sound as the physical
            entity it was, before it was extinguished.</p>

        <p>The adventurer, after a few hours of instruction, paid the old teacher and set off on his
            way. <location ref="Indoranyon" visitable="no">Indoranyon</location>, <person
                ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person>'s stronghold, was not far from <location
                ref="Sadrith Mora" visitable="yes">Sadrith Mora</location>, and he soon saw the
            blight and ruin that was the battlemage's calling card. Delving into the depths of the
            ruins, <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person> was set upon by the
            servitors of <person ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person>, living and undead. With his
            enchanted ebony blade, he cut through legions before facing the master himself in the
            desolate main hall.</p>

        <p><person ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person> bowed to his adversary sardonically, and then
            prepared to unleash a fireball to incinerate him. Before he had uttered the first word
            of the spell, he suddenly found that all the creaking and sighing of the ruins around
            him had been stilled. He opened his voice to speak, but there was no sound. <person
                ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person> took his time, strolling across the
            length of the hall, before dispatching the battlemage with one stroke of his blade.</p>

        <p>The adventurer rushed back to the <location ref="Tribunal Temple" visitable="yes"
                >Tribunal Temple</location> where he had received his quest, accepted the gold and
            the thanks, and was back in his house in <location ref="Gnisis" visitable="yes"
                >Gnisis</location> but a few days later. His wife <person ref="Liah">Liah</person>
            was beside herself with worry.</p>

        <p>“All I could do night after night is toss and turn. I kept imagining you burned to ashes
            by that battlemage, and where would that leave me? Do we have enough gold that I could
            support myself if you, <person ref="Saint Seryn">Saint Seryn</person> let it not be so,
            were killed during one of these jaunts? I don't think so. Why couldn't you get a nice
            position at the <group ref="Fighters Guild">Fighters Guild</group> right here in town? I
            hear they're looking for a trainer for the <group ref="Imperial Guard">Imperial
                Guard</group>. I know, I know, you want a life of adventure and danger and freedom,
            but if you'd only take one moment to think of me, stuck here all by myself, worrying
            about you. I suppose you'd like it if I took more of an interest in your work, but it's
            like I was telling Ser <person ref="Calissiah Vignum">Calissiah Vignum</person> the
            other day, I said <person ref="Calissiah Vignum">Calissah</person>, what good is a
            husband--”</p>

        <p><person ref="Liah">Liah</person> continued to talk, deaf to the fact that her words were
            dead before they left her mouth. <person ref="Oristian Silverthorn">Silverthorn</person>
            smiled and nodded his head, enjoying the silence. He could have killed <person
                ref="Egroamaro">Egroamaro</person> without the spell, he considered, but he could
            not have survived his wife.</p>
    </contents>
    <consoleID xmlid="bookskill_illusion2">bookskill_illusion2</consoleID>
</Book>
